Privacy Policy  

The privacy of our visitors is important to us.

We recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit Ask Jeeves.net site, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL, etc), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site, also Remarketing with Google Analytics.

**Cookies**

* **Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to AskJeeves.net site.**
* **Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads, based on their visit to AskJeeves.net site.**
* **Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative [opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).)**

Transparency and choice  
  
People have different privacy concerns. Our goal is to be clear about what information we collect, so that you can make meaningful choices about how it is used. For example, you can: [Visit your Google Account History](https://www.google.com/settings/accounthistory?hl=en) for settings that allow you to control the collection of personal information from Google services, such as Search, YouTube and Location History. Review and control certain types of information tied to your Google Account by using Google Dashboard. View and edit your preferences about the Google ads shown to you on Google and across the web, such as which categories might interest you, using Ads Settings. You can also opt out of certain Google advertising services here. Adjust how the Profile associated with your Google Account appears to others. Control who you share information with through your Google Account. Take information associated with your Google Account out of many of our services. Choose whether your Profile name and Profile photo appear in shared endorsements that appear in ads. You may also set your browser to block all cookies, including cookies associated with our services, or to indicate when a cookie is being set by us. However, itâ€™s important to remember that many of our services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. For example, we may not remember your language preferences. Back to top Information you share Many of our services let you share information with others. Remember that when you share information publicly, it may be indexable by search engines, including Google. Our services provide you with different options on sharing and removing your content.

Google Analytics

Google Analytics generates statistics about visitors to websites, such as the number of page views or times of peak traffic. If you don't want your anonymous browser data to be collected by Google Analytics when you visit sites that use Google Analytics, you can install an opt-out in your web browser [opt-out of Google Analytics](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/)
